{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.noShow.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268796312","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268796312"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268804890","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268804890"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" a2d91eb2-7a28-4ecd-b517-318e80eaeb08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268805114","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268805114"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" a2d91eb2-7a28-4ecd-b517-318e80eaeb08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268806081","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268806081"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" a2d91eb2-7a28-4ecd-b517-318e80eaeb08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268807354","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268807354"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" a2d91eb2-7a28-4ecd-b517-318e80eaeb08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268810225","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268810225"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" a2d91eb2-7a28-4ecd-b517-318e80eaeb08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268811073","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268811073"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" a2d91eb2-7a28-4ecd-b517-318e80eaeb08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268811252","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268811251"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" a2d91eb2-7a28-4ecd-b517-318e80eaeb08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268811326","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268811326"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" a2d91eb2-7a28-4ecd-b517-318e80eaeb08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.wa.noShow.16","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268838853","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268838853"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" a2d91eb2-7a28-4ecd-b517-318e80eaeb08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268843754","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268843752"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" a2d91eb2-7a28-4ecd-b517-318e80eaeb08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.wa.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268851909","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268851908"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" a2d91eb2-7a28-4ecd-b517-318e80eaeb08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268855723","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268855723"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" a2d91eb2-7a28-4ecd-b517-318e80eaeb08"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.wa.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268870154","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268870153"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 1938732f-03c4-4e6d-a579-aff88d610849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.wa.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WAZI"," userResponse":" START_WAZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.wa.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268871612","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268871611"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 1938732f-03c4-4e6d-a579-aff88d610849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.wa.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.wa.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268872684","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268872684"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 1938732f-03c4-4e6d-a579-aff88d610849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.wa.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAZI"," userResponse":" WAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.wa.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268882270","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268882270"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 1938732f-03c4-4e6d-a579-aff88d610849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.wa.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wawe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.wa.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268883346","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268883345"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 1938732f-03c4-4e6d-a579-aff88d610849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.wa.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wawe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAWE"," userResponse":" WAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.wa.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268886786","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268886786"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 1938732f-03c4-4e6d-a579-aff88d610849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.wa.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAUA"," userResponse":" WAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.wa.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268887846","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268887845"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 1938732f-03c4-4e6d-a579-aff88d610849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.wa.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAUA"," userResponse":" WAUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.wa.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268892864","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268892863"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 1938732f-03c4-4e6d-a579-aff88d610849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.wa.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wavu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVU"," userResponse":" WAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.wa.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268893923","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268893923"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 1938732f-03c4-4e6d-a579-aff88d610849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.wa.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wavu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAVU"," userResponse":" WAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.wa.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268898036","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268898035"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 1938732f-03c4-4e6d-a579-aff88d610849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.wa.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wake"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.wa.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268899092","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268899091"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 1938732f-03c4-4e6d-a579-aff88d610849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.wa.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wake"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.wa.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268901908","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268901908"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 1938732f-03c4-4e6d-a579-aff88d610849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.wa.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANA"," userResponse":" WANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.wa.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268902053","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268902053"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 1938732f-03c4-4e6d-a579-aff88d610849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.wa.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.wa.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268903054","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268903054"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 1938732f-03c4-4e6d-a579-aff88d610849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.wa.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wale"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.wa.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268905491","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268905490"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 1938732f-03c4-4e6d-a579-aff88d610849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.wa.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wale"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALE"," userResponse":" WALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.wa.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268912522","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268912522"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 1938732f-03c4-4e6d-a579-aff88d610849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.wa.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wapi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.wa.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268913609","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268913608"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 1938732f-03c4-4e6d-a579-aff88d610849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.wa.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" wapi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAPI"," userResponse":" WAPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.wa.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268916784","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268916784"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 1938732f-03c4-4e6d-a579-aff88d610849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.wa.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waje"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAJE"," userResponse":" WAJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.wa.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268917836","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268917835"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 1938732f-03c4-4e6d-a579-aff88d610849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.wa.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" waje"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAJE"," userResponse":" WAJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.wa.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268924123","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268924122"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 1938732f-03c4-4e6d-a579-aff88d610849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.wa.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" watu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.wa.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268925197","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268925197"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 1938732f-03c4-4e6d-a579-aff88d610849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.wa.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" watu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.wa.rand.42","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268928701","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268928700"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 1938732f-03c4-4e6d-a579-aff88d610849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.wa.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" watu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268928815","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268928815"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 1938732f-03c4-4e6d-a579-aff88d610849"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.wa.rand.42"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" watu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATU"," userResponse":" WATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268942343","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268942343"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 6d9bbd87-76af-4bde-9a5a-9abe911edb99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268954142","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268954142"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 6d9bbd87-76af-4bde-9a5a-9abe911edb99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" END"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268954449","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268954449"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 6d9bbd87-76af-4bde-9a5a-9abe911edb99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268954588","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268954588"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 6d9bbd87-76af-4bde-9a5a-9abe911edb99"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.ko.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268962766","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268962765"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 43e7e957-14c2-4528-b2a3-ca72a9479830"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.ko.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mshtuko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSHTUKO"," userResponse":" MSHTUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.ko.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268966178","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268966178"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 43e7e957-14c2-4528-b2a3-ca72a9479830"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.ko.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dadako"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADAKO"," userResponse":" DADAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.ko.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268969348","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268969348"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 43e7e957-14c2-4528-b2a3-ca72a9479830"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.ko.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mfuko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUKO"," userResponse":" MFUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.ko.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268972285","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268972284"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 43e7e957-14c2-4528-b2a3-ca72a9479830"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.ko.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yako"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKO"," userResponse":" YAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.ko.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268975289","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268975289"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 43e7e957-14c2-4528-b2a3-ca72a9479830"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.ko.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ziko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIKO"," userResponse":" ZIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.ko.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268978443","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268978443"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 43e7e957-14c2-4528-b2a3-ca72a9479830"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.ko.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" koko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KOKO"," userResponse":" KOKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.ko.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268981366","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268981366"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 43e7e957-14c2-4528-b2a3-ca72a9479830"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.ko.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" yuko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YUKO"," userResponse":" YUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.ko.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268984376","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268984375"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 43e7e957-14c2-4528-b2a3-ca72a9479830"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.ko.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kicheko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHEKO"," userResponse":" KICHEKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.ko.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268987551","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268987551"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 43e7e957-14c2-4528-b2a3-ca72a9479830"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.ko.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" jiko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIKO"," userResponse":" JIKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.ko.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268990531","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268990530"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 43e7e957-14c2-4528-b2a3-ca72a9479830"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.ko.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiboko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" KIBOKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::end.wrd.ko.rand.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268993894","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268993893"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 43e7e957-14c2-4528-b2a3-ca72a9479830"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.ko.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" kiboko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268993949","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268993949"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 43e7e957-14c2-4528-b2a3-ca72a9479830"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.ko.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kiboko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIBOKO"," userResponse":" KIBOKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549268999761","data":{"timestamp":" 1549268999760"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 43e7e957-14c2-4528-b2a3-ca72a9479830"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__end.wrd.ko.rand.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" kiboko"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.ko.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269021038","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269021038"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 70db3b77-63ac-4614-99b0-2a595d90a497"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.ko.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kwako_jiko_zako"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.ko.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269027702","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269027702"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 70db3b77-63ac-4614-99b0-2a595d90a497"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.ko.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_yuko_zako_dadako"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.ko.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269034341","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269034340"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 70db3b77-63ac-4614-99b0-2a595d90a497"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.ko.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_lako_mshtuko_babako"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.ko.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269040985","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269040984"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 70db3b77-63ac-4614-99b0-2a595d90a497"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.ko.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o2_babako_huko_soko"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.ko.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269047648","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269047647"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 70db3b77-63ac-4614-99b0-2a595d90a497"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.ko.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kwako_mifuko_jiko"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.ko.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269054277","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269054277"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 70db3b77-63ac-4614-99b0-2a595d90a497"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.ko.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_ziko_zako_chako"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.ko.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269060939","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269060939"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 70db3b77-63ac-4614-99b0-2a595d90a497"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.ko.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_zako_mfuko_mshtuko"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.ko.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269067592","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269067592"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 70db3b77-63ac-4614-99b0-2a595d90a497"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.ko.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o2_msisimuko_yuko_soko"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.ko.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269074233","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269074232"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 70db3b77-63ac-4614-99b0-2a595d90a497"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.ko.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o2_msisimko_soko_mfuko"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.ko.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269080830","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269080829"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 70db3b77-63ac-4614-99b0-2a595d90a497"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.ko.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_kwako_ambako_yuko"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:end.wrd.ko.show.9","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269093960","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269093959"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 70db3b77-63ac-4614-99b0-2a595d90a497"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.ko.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_kwako_ambako_yuko"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269098644","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269098643"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 70db3b77-63ac-4614-99b0-2a595d90a497"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.ko.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_kwako_ambako_yuko"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ko.noShow.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269111479","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269111479"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 70db3b77-63ac-4614-99b0-2a595d90a497"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.ko.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_kwako_ambako_yuko"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269117167","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269117167"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 70db3b77-63ac-4614-99b0-2a595d90a497"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.ko.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_kwako_ambako_yuko"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ko.noShow.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269131875","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269131875"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 70db3b77-63ac-4614-99b0-2a595d90a497"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.ko.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_kwako_ambako_yuko"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269137459","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269137458"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 70db3b77-63ac-4614-99b0-2a595d90a497"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.ko.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_kwako_ambako_yuko"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:end.wrd.ko.noShow.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269145813","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269145813"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 70db3b77-63ac-4614-99b0-2a595d90a497"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.ko.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_kwako_ambako_yuko"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549269150418","data":{"timestamp":" 1549269150417"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190204_112614"," gameId":" 70db3b77-63ac-4614-99b0-2a595d90a497"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_end.wrd.ko.show.9"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_kwako_ambako_yuko"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}